as a romantic things on the shade yo yo
yo welcome to the car a i periscope we
are here I'm George and I'm here with
any hey we are manufacturing pandas I
don't think anyone heard that no was in
our periscope yeah so these are panda
cases we have many many many panda cases
we have many more than just what's here
[Music]
so I'm picking out the ones that are
good
many many Panda cases you see this is a
good one it doesn't have any of that
raft crap on it you see this is a bad
one because crap on it this one is no
crap so it's all 3d printed yeah we were
originally going to stand for the cases
we have a lot of sanding equipment setup
but sanding sucks you want to do videos
for comedy I please do videos yeah let's
get the scale
bro pandas are a raft good get some
pretty one and show them like what they
look like let me break them off commas
are pandas oh these are pandas look this
is what a bunch of pandas looks like you
can we manufacture them I'm sure they
have plenty of hands
so this is the Kama side of the case
with a homicide Panda sighs okay we've
got to go get the scam to figure out how
many of these we so we've manufactured
we've we're not gonna announce the exact
order number but I will say that it's
over 1,000 and I will say also that it's
not over 9,000 so we sold somewhere
between one and nine thousand panels so
yeah so that time for these guys to
start shipping are the first finished
pandas are right here this is this
little batch of six right here
panda moaning you see this is a sanding
panda so some people are going to get
sand in pandas but yeah
Oh excellent you know they they watch
you after you buy a scale so that's 148
grams this is hair yes will tear it to
the box ten pandas weighs 34 grams or
more tracks is liars okay so 20 pandas
is 70 grams let's just do 25 so I can do
math easier 20
[Applause]
so 25 is 8686 on a nice number what I
think actually I want to fix my phone to
knock so 86 is what's the best way to
contact me right here on periscope if
you have something secret to tell me we
don't like secrets um so I don't know
okay so 86 is 25 we should write that
down somewhere 2586 all creased is
coming along well we got with our top
guy on the prius 686 is 25 100 is 344
that's a better way thing okay so that's
$240.00 yeah Wow these things I thought
there were a lot more in these boxes
then alright so I'm gonna sort them
between good and you know like the truth
about being CEO of the company is when
things are known people say like not my
problem
well it's my problem well what's what's
yeah that's always my problem you know
it's never not my problem is always my
problem
like can you page 344 we should catch
these off in batches of 100
is it possible to pay a visit to our
office Renato goal that's how can you
get involved with commenting on media if
you make good stuff we'll tweet it
I love sweater what
filling it with water Archimedes would
be proud shut that door my periscope and
then we can see if they're scanning us
and this isn't actually melts you know
we gotta finish the story
and this doesn't we were originally
gonna call it you know okay so what
we're doing is for those who performed
these are cases that are gonna go on
Candice we're gonna get 688 grams
I'm just sorting here
where are the boards well the board got
delivered this morning to one of the
places that's doing final pandas we do
have we have 1,000 boys in holding after
these ones get shipped out we're gonna
authorize finishing machine so what we
bought and what's getting here today is
is is a ultrasonic wash and may be so
handy cases are 3d printed and then
they're glued together because there's
no user serviceable parts inside this is
this is what the new logic boards look
like guys yeah originally gonna do white
and black boards why don't we go with
the white boards so white board hey
Dennis to get something little white
board you know it was hand soldered
know the scale turned off watch what
saved my tear oh this is a tragedy okay
you sure they weigh the same I don't
know what's the manufacturing varium to
these things
what Sterilite we don't do we don't do
marketing and we don't do branding we
don't do advertising because build a
good product and window we're not I'm
not gonna like spam people with
advertising like awareness is one thing
another thing if you have things that
are like 10x better I promise start to
succeed a lot of people start saying you
know dude I have a self-driving car
right like if something people are gonna
talk no marketing when you have
if you don't have the wild things on ya
[Music]
[Applause]
how many cars did I trade the first part
or a lot for just one car but also 3 :
right so when you trade one phone for
our car and three phones you definitely
win when you read these do we have left
none they're all gone these were mostly
like we wanted to see how people would
react to Panda we're going to see is
really and of course everybody be paid
for a panda we'll be getting a recipe
and contest winners will also be getting
red seas
it's a whole lot easier this is a lot
and this is not a super complicated
product it's not like a phone or
anything but it's not that simple I'm
868 so should I be at 8:59 six no I will
put in once more for good luck
[Music]
I'll pass the hots goodness yeah we're
gonna try to get Bauer's energy please
Kate do you have more commas for me to
break off you know tripod for me
looks broken broken
she's broken she's got like that crap on
and then our ultrasonic washer gets here
to make sure we should we show them a
few nice folks on periscope the
ultrasonic Walker
yeah these are all comma hit a chest
strap we're not before home so this is
what it looks like see that's combo this
is with a panda production clean whoops
everything one-handed for you guys man
pre this is going well
we have our best folks on three
we're fat Tommy gets contaminated by
panda look at all those coppers
well the Civic getting feet or capturing
the city party has increased talkers oh
you mean more increase than the six
percent we're 12 people no we don't plan
to ship any firmware updates at least
for a long time to increase torque
beyond is so smooth is it yeah we're
working with silky smooth um so if you
see Rick Blass in the chat he's alright
he's our controls engineer it might be
my soundcloud I do a stock um he's the
guy who's working our silky smooth
controls we also have an intern coming
starting soon as well self controls is
about to get really good yeah Rick does
a great job he does yeah how much for a
feature
hey if you you know what I'm at this
stage of my rap career where if you can
get any hits and views first together I
got six teens all Damon the a8 not known
as an a8 we're ghost riding for the
masses yeah oh yeah all right so what
buys me an RA I will make open power buy
me a personal all right now for combat
yeah I mean all right I'll make I'll
make
music Rai and you really got something
going yeah that's not the largeness no
okay you step Mercedes s-class is pretty
nice
yeah rep C is going to be two boards
like razz be but watch what's what's
gonna what's going to upset the fine
folks about the rough seas and the
boards they're not Sokka - no they are
actually soldered together yeah
what is the Kanda um check out our
medium if you want to do these RFC's um
so let's see this is our I see that I
was just arrived to see like this run to
finish for overseas notice the case
looks a little bit differently all right
which printer we use or tracks em to
hundreds all the prototypes are get
shoulder for the texture they're sealed
in the just going here you guys know
that our data center right so data
center
[Music]
yeah this is really good yeah simulation
is a bad thing and it's certainly a good
place to test what you're doing there is
you're similar what is the idea RAF you
see that this plugs into the mobile on
the Honda this is will you plug in the
wire and this is where you plug in your
panel so it lets your Panda connect to
what it lets your Panda connect to the
special place in the Honda that you can
control the car from so this is a
giraffe we're just gonna open source
them le timer is already selling stuff
that's a lot like this
open boards that I check it out so you
know you might try now we're just gonna
probably open-source this anyone who
wants to can make and sell them updates
for open pilot how's it been in the
giant panda should we should we should
we okay
giant panda was what you know we were
not planning to support giant pandas
long term um there's a lot that we
haven't announced but I wouldn't invest
too much into giant pandas were we're
just really for us to test pandas and
for red deep into holders they're not
really gonna work with rescue panda um
we have better stop planned than giant
pandas we can't win that's awesome what
next animal is coming up well there were
comic koalas briefly no no I think they
actually cancelled find a lot of bugs in
what you know what are you what box well
do you mean bugs or do you mean like
like you know places where you have to
disengage city sneak infrastructure
changes I don't think that's really
worth it like the truth about
self-driving is the whole farm part is
interoperating with humans like if you'd
have to make a change that's so radical
anytime soon in like very restricted
areas in some cities we promised or
should we call our store the Kabul zoo
zoo so what I'm trying to figure out now
is like when I'm breaking these things
off or some of them predestined to be
bad or is it that way I think that's
what it might be but some is what folks
have you found the wrong path finally
she's one get Bob if there are real bugs
will absolutely pick some oh I saw the
one about the rearview mirror yeah what
war is that the next release sorry about
that
it was uh they're just just stupid no
the disabling of the really narrow boat
didn't work in this set in the settings
yeah people like disabling your regular
um
ego but one plus three it's really not
useful Leslie Qi it's a bit more useful
you've been around for a while that's
definitely true you found you found bugs
still in open fire yeah let me know let
me know what they are kind of stuff is
there gonna be an EOS for maybe probably
yeah I mean we have we have some things
planned I think they're gonna need an
update in the US on it Oh Neal yeah I
mean we have we have all the updater
intercept replacement so if we do decide
that we need to modify the underlying
operating system if you see there's no
sub module and open file install PI
extra pie extra lets us change the
Python packages without having to change
the operating system
[Applause]
alright guys this is getting difficult
whitby holding this and doing things
you're taking a ride over self-driving a
Pittsburgh how was it good yeah it's
it's a work in progress
yeah I've been an uber self-driving car
as well nothing too impressive so yeah
I'm gonna let you all go for now we'll
be back on later if we get another cool
step in the manufacturing we want to be
real open with our panda manufacturing
processes and know to everybody who
ordered it you will be getting them
recently yeah I'll definitely meet our
four to twelve week deadline thanks
everyone
all right
swipe down to stop